Guide to the Sarah Brown Ingersoll Cooper Papers, 1813-1921
Cooper, Sarah Brown Ingersoll Papers, 1813-1921
- Series I. Correspondence and Personal Material
  - General Correspondence
    - Correspondence and Personal Material, Nov. 1, 1885-Nov. 14, 1885 (Box 3, Folder 37)
    - Correspondence and Personal Material, Nov. 15, 1885-Nov.29, 1885 (Box 3, Folder 38)
    - Correspondence and Personal Material: includes a letter from Halsey Cooper to his mother on his 57th birthday and his suicide note; Dec. 1, 1885-Dec. 12, 1885 (Box 3, Folder 39)
    - Correspondence and Personal Material: includes sympathy letters to Sarah and Harriet and the account book of funds raised for Sarah and Halsey Cooper's mortgage; Dec. 13, 1885-Dec. 28, 1885 (Box 3, Folder 40)
    - A Refutation- letter from Sarah Cooper to John Morton, Surveyor of Internal Revenue Service, in defence of her husband 1886 (Box 7, Folder 30)
    - Correspondence and Personal Material, Jan. 1886 (Box 4, Folder 1)
    - Correspondence and Personal Material, Feb. 1886 (Box 4, Folder 2)
    - Correspondence and Personal Material, Mar. 1886-June 1886 (Box 4, Folder 3)
    - Correspondence and Personal Material: includes a letter from Emily Faithfull encouraging Sarah to write to her; includes a letter from Sarah to Halsey Cooper on their thirty-first wedding anniversary; July 1886-Aug. 1886 (Box 4, Folder 4)
    - Correspondence and Personal Material, Sept. 1886-Dec. 1886 (Box 4, Folder 5)
    - Correspondence and Personal Material, Jan. 1887-June 1887 (Box 4, Folder 6)
    - Correspondence and Personal Material, July 1887-Oct. 1887 (Box 4, Folder 7)
    - Correspondence and Personal Material, Nov. 1887-Dec. 1887 (Box 4, Folder 8)
    - Correspondence and Personal Material: includes a letter from Jane Stanford regarding a letter from Susan B. Anthony; Jan 1888.-Feb. 1888 (Box 4, Folder 9)
    - Correspondence and Personal Material, Mar. 1888-May 1888 (Box 4, Folder 10)
    - Correspondence and Personal Material, June 1, 1888-June 18, 1888 (Box 4, Folder 11)
    - Correspondence and Personal Material, June 19, 1888-June 30, 1888 (Box 4, Folder 12)
    - Correspondence and Personal Material, July 1888 (Box 4, Folder 13)
    - Correspondence and Personal Material, Aug. 1888-Oct. 1888 (Box 4, Folder 14)
    - Correspondence and Personal Material, Nov. 1888-Dec. 1888 (Box 4, Folder 15)
    - Correspondence and Personal Material, Jan. 1889-Mar. 1889 (Box 4, Folder 16)
    - Correspondence and Personal Material, Apr. 1889-June 1889 (Box 4, Folder 17)
    - Correspondence and Personal Material, July 1889 (Box 4, Folder 18)
    - Correspondence and Personal Material, Aug. 1889 (Box 4, Folder 19)
    - Correspondence and Personal Material, Sept. 1889-Nov. 1889 (Box 4, Folder 20)
    - Correspondence and Personal Material, Dec. 1889 (Box 4, Folder 21)
    - Correspondence and Personal Material, Jan. 1890-Feb. 1890 (Box 4, Folder 22)
    - Correspondence and Personal Material, Mar. 1890 (Box 4, Folder 23)
    - Correspondence and Personal Material: includes a letter from William Sheldon which addresses the national and international influences of Sarah's Kindergarten work; Apr. 1890-May 1890 (Box 4, Folder 24)
    - Correspondence and Personal Material, June 1890-Aug. 1890 (Box 4, Folder 25)
    - Correspondence and Personal Material, Sept. 1890-Oct. 1890 (Box 4, Folder 26)
    - Correspondence and Personal Material, Nov. 1890-Dec. 1890 (Box 4, Folder 27)
    - Correspondence and Personal Material, Jan. 1891 (Box 4, Folder 28)
    - Correspondence and Personal Material, Feb. 1891-Mar. 1891 (Box 4, Folder 29)
    - Correspondence and Personal Material, Apr. 1891 (Box 4, Folder 30)
    - Correspondence and Personal Material: includes a printed copy of endorsements of the California Educational Review, including one by Sarah; letter from John Eaton; May 1, 1891-May 15, 1891 (Box 4, Folder 31)
    - Correspondence and Personal Material, May 16, 1891-May 30, 1891 (Box 4, Folder 32)
    - Correspondence and Personal Material, June 1891-July 1891 (Box 4, Folder 33)
    - Correspondence and Personal Material, Aug. 1891-Sept. 1891 (Box 4, Folder 34)
    - Correspondence and Personal Material, Oct. 1891-Nov. 1891 (Box 4, Folder 35)
    - Correspondence and Personal Material, Dec. 1891 (Box 4, Folder 36)
    - Correspondence and Personal Material, Jan. 1892 (Box 4, Folder 37)
    - Correspondence and Personal Material, Feb. 1892 (Box 4, Folder 38)
    - Correspondence and Personal Material, Mar. 1892 (Box 4, Folder 39)
    - Correspondence and Personal Material, Apr. 1892 (Box 4, Folder 40)
    - Correspondence and Personal Material: includes a notice regarding Sarah's appointment to the Advisory Council of the Women's Branch of the World's Congress Auxiliary; May 2, 1892-May 22, 1892 (Box 4, Folder 41)
    - Correspondence and Personal Material, May 23 1892-May 31, 1892 (Box 4, Folder 42)
    - Correspondence and Personal Material, June 1,1892-June 10, 1892 (Box 5, Folder 1)
    - Correspondence and Personal Material, June 11,1892-June 30, 1892 (Box 4, Folder 2)
    - Correspondence and Personal Material: includes a letter about opening a kindergarten in British Columbia; July 1892 (Box 5, Folder 3)
    - Correspondence and Personal Material, Aug. 1892 (Box 5, Folder 4)
    - Correspondence and Personal Material: includes several letters from Rachel Foster Avery in regards to the International Kindergarten Union joining the National Council of Women; Sept. 1892 (Box 5, Folder 5)
    - Correspondence and Personal Material: includes several letters from Rachel Foster Avery in regards to the International Kindergarten Union joining the National Council of Women;, Oct. 1892 (Box 5, Folder 6)
    - Correspondence and Personal Material, Nov. 1892 (Box 5, Folder 7)
    - Correspondence and Personal Material, Dec. 1892 (Box 5, Folder 8)
    - Biographical information on Sarah Cooper 1893-1898 (Box 7, Folder 22)
    - Correspondence and Personal Material, Jan. 1893 (Box 5, Folder 9)
    - Correspondence and Personal Material: includes a letter about Sarah giving a talk on Public Schools and the Kindergarten System at the World's Congress of Representatitve Women; includes several letters from Sarah Stewart, Vice President of the International Kindergarten Union; Feb. 1893 (Box 5, Folder 10)
    - Correspondence and Personal Material: includes several letters from California Secretary of State E.G. Waite about the Women's Suffrage Bill and the bill to pension teachers; includes two letters from Sarah Stewart; Mar. 1893 (Box 5, Folder 11)
    - Correspondence and Personal Material: includes several letters from May Wright Sewall in regards to the building space given to the National Council of Women; includes a letter from Sarah Stewart; includes several letters from Rachel Foster Avery; Apr. 1893 (Box 5, Folder 12)
    - Correspondence and Personal Material: includes several letters about Sarah speaking at a chapel service at the University of Chicago; includes several letters from Philip D. Armour - a childhood friend of Sarah's from Cazenovia and head of the Armour Mission and Institute, the Armour Glue Works and various Railroad lines; May 1893 (Box 5, Folder 13)
    - Correspondence and Personal Material, June 1893 (Box 5, Folder 14)
    - Correspondence and Personal Material: includes a letter from Armour and Company and a check for $250 and several letters from Philip D. Armour; July 1893 (Box 5, Folder 15)
    - Correspondence and Personal Material, Aug. 1893 (Box 5, Folder 16)
    - Correspondence and Personal Material: includes several letters from Philip D. Armour; Sept. 1893 (Box 5, Folder 17)
    - Correspondence and Personal Material: includes letter from May Wright Sewall about getting a signed picture of Sarah for her photo collection; Oct. 1893 (Box 5, Folder 18)
    - Correspondence and Personal Material: includes several letters from Sarah to Philip D. Armour concerning Sarah's desire to start an institution similar to the Armour Institute and a request for him to invest money in her projects; Nov. 1893 (Box 5, Folder 19)
    - Correspondence and Personal Material, Dec. 1893 (Box 5, Folder 20)
    - Correspondence and Personal Material: includes a letter from the Armour Institute about Sarah's new school; Jan. 1894 (Box 5, Folder 21)
    - Correspondence and Personal Material: includes a letter from Philip D. Armour about his upcoming visit to San Francisco; includes a letter from Sarah Stewart; includes a letter from Anna Craig from Brigham Young Academy regarding kindergarten education in Utah; Feb. 1894 (Box 5, Folder 22)
    - Correspondence and Personal Material: includes several letters in regards to Sarah starting an institution similar to Hull House Association in San Francisco; Mar. 1894 (Box 5, Folder 23)
    - Correspondence and Personal Material: includes a letter from Rachel Foster Avery addressed to the women at the California Midwinter International Exposition; Apr. 1894 (Box 5, Folder 24)
    - Correspondence and Personal Material, May 1894 (Box 5, Folder 25)
    - Correspondence and Personal Material: includes a letter from the Armour Institute; includes a letter from the Golden Gate Union requesting Sarah to speak; includes a letter from E.G. Waite regarding his political career; includes a letter from Charles F. Johnson in regards to Sarah writing an article for his upcoming book; June 1, 1894-June 18, 1894 (Box 5, Folder 26)
    - Correspondence and Personal Material, June 19-30, 1894 (Box 5, Folder 27)
    - Correspondence and Personal Material, July 1894 (Box 5, Folder 28)
    - Correspondence and Personal Material: includes a letter from H.J. McCoy in regards to Sarah giving an address at the opening of the San Francisco Y.M.C.A.; August 1894 (Box 5, Folder 29)
    - Correspondence and Personal Material: includes a letter from H.J. McCoy thanking Sarah for her address at the Y.M.C.A. and asking her to give another; Sept. 1894 (Box 5, Folder 30)
    - Correspondence and Personal Material: includes several letters from Philip D. Armour; includes a letter from Phoebe Hearst; Oct. 1894 (Box 5, Folder 31)
    - Correspondence and Personal Material: includes several letters from Philip D. Armour; includes a letter from Sarah Stewart; Nov. 1894 (Box 5, Folder 32)
    - Correspondence and Personal Material; includes a letter from Sarah Stewart; Dec. 1894 (Box 5, Folder 33)
    - Correspondence and Personal Material: includes a letter from May Wright Sewall; Jan. 1895 (Box 5, Folder 34)
    - Correspondence and Personal Material: includes a letter from Philip D. Armour; includes a letter from Phoebe Hearst in which she refuses to pay Susan B. Anthony's expenses to the Pacific Coast Congress; includes a letter from Ada VanPelt about the busy schedule of Charlotte Perkins Stetson (Charlotte Perkins Gilman); Feb. 1895-Mar. 1895 (Box 5, Folder 35)
    - Correspondence and Personal Material, Apr. 1895-May 1895 (Box 5, Folder 36)
    - Correspondence and Personal Material, June 1895 (Box 5, Folder 37)
    - Correspondence and Personal Material: includes a letter from Philip D. Armour; July 1895-Aug. 1895 (Box 5, Folder 38)
    - Correspondence and Personal Material: includes a letter from Charlotte Perkins Stetson about her and Jane Addams' work with the Hull House Association; Sept. 1895 (Box 5, Folder 39)
    - Correspondence and Personal Material: includes a letter from Sarah to Harriet regarding Harriet's trip with Anna Howard Shaw; includes a letter inviting Sarah to dine with Adolph Sutro, the mayor of San Francisco; Oct. 1, 1895-Oct. 16, 1895 (Box 5, Folder 40)
    - Correspondence and Personal Material, Oct. 17, 1895-Oct. 31, 1895 (Box 5, Folder 41)
    - Correspondence and Personal Material: includes a letter from Charlotte Perkins Stetson about Jane Addams and the Hull House Association; Nov. 1895 (Box 5, Folder 42)
    - Correspondence and Personal Material: includes a letter from Phoebe Hearst regarding her financial contributions to Sarah's kindergartens; Dec. 1895 (Box 5, Folder 43)
    - Correspondence and Personal Material: Letters from Lucy and Mary Anthony; 1896 (Box 6, Folder 48)
    - Correspondence and Personal Material: includes a letter from Phoebe Hearst; Jan. 1896 (Box 5, Folder 44)
    - Correspondence and Personal Material: includes a letter from Charlotte Perkins Stetson which discusses her latest trip and mentions Susan B. Anthony and Anna Howard Shaw; includes a letter about prostitutes in San Francisco who advertise in the daily paper; includes a letter from Rachel Foster Avery requesting an autographed picture of Sarah; Feb. 1896 (Box 5, Folder 45)
    - Correspondence and Personal Material: includes a letter from Phoebe Hearst; Mar. 1896 (Box 5, Folder 46)
    - Correspondence and Personal Material: includes several letters from Phoebe Hearst; Apr. 1896 (Box 6, Folder 1)
    - Correspondence and Personal Material: includes a letter concerning Americans condemned by the courts of South Africa; includes several letters from the Woman's Suffrage Association; May 1896 (Box 6, Folder 2)
    - Correspondence and Personal Material, June 1896 (Box 6, Folder 3)
    - Correspondence and Personal Material, July 1896 (Box 6, Folder 4)
    - Correspondence and Personal Material: includes a letter from Mary Lowe Dickinson, President of the National Council of Women; Aug. 1896 (Box 6, Folder 5)
    - Correspondence and Personal Material: includes a letter from Philip D. Armour; Sept. 1896 (Box 6, Folder 6)
    - Correspondence and Personal Material: includes a letter from Sarah's sister Harriet Skilton expressing concern over Harriet Cooper's mental condition; Oct. 1896 (Box 6, Folder 7)
    - Correspondence and Personal Material: includes several letters from Sarah to her sister Harriet Skilton forshadowing her death; includes several letters from Harriet Skilton expressing concern about Harriet Cooper's condition; Nov. 1896 (Box 6, Folder 8)
    - Correspondence and Personal Material: includes several letters from Sarah to her sister Harriet Skilton forshadowing her death; includes several letters from Harriet Skilton expressing concern about Harriet Cooper's condition; includes a brief eulogy of Sarah; Dec. 1896 (Box 6, Folder 9)
    - Letters of Condolence to Ellen Henrotin, President of the General Federation of Women's Clubs, 1896-1897 (Box 6, Folder 10)
    - Correspondence and Personal Material: including information on wills and the Cooper estate, Jan. 1897 (Box 6, Folder 11)
    - Correspondence and Personal Material - including information on wills and the Cooper estate, Feb. 1897 (Box 6, Folder 12)
    - Correspondence and Personal Material - including information on wills and the Cooper estate, Mar. 1897 (Box 6, Folder 13)
    - Correspondence and Personal Material - including information on wills and the Cooper estate, Apr. 1897 (Box 6, Folder 14)
    - Correspondence and Personal Material - including information on wills and the Cooper estate, May 2, 1897-May 22, 1897 (Box 6, Folder 15)
    - Correspondence and Personal Material - including information on wills and the Cooper estate, May 25, 1897-May 31, 1897 (Box 6, Folder 16)
    - Correspondence and Personal Material - including information on wills and the Cooper estate, June 1,1897-June 22, 1897 (Box 6, Folder 17)
    - Correspondence and Personal Material - including information on wills and the Cooper estate, June 25, 1897 (Box 6, Folder 18)
    - Correspondence and Personal Material - including information on wills and the Cooper estate, June 26, 1897-June 31, 1897 (Box 6, Folder 19)
    - Correspondence and Personal Material - including information on wills and the Cooper estate, Aug. 1897-Dec. 1897 (Box 6, Folder 20)
    - Correspondence and Personal Material - including information on wills and the Cooper estate, Jan. 1898-Feb. 1898 (Box 6, Folder 21)
    - Correspondence and Personal Material - including information on wills and the Cooper estate, Mar. 1898 (Box 6, Folder 22)
    - Correspondence and Personal Material - including information on wills and the Cooper estate, Apr. 1898-July 1898 (Box 6, Folder 23)
    - Correspondence and Personal Material - including information on wills and the Cooper estate, Aug. 1898 (Box 6, Folder 24)
    - Correspondence and Personal Material - including information on wills and the Cooper estate, Sept. 1898-Oct. 1898 (Box 6, Folder 25)
    - Correspondence and Personal Material - including information on wills and the Cooper estate, Nov. 1898 (Box 6, Folder 26)
    - Correspondence and Personal Material - including information on wills and the Cooper estate, Dec. 1898 (Box 6, Folder 27)
    - Correspondence and Personal Material, 1899-1918 (Box 6, Folder 28)
    - Undated correspondence to Halsey Fenimore Cooper from Sarah Cooper (Box 6, Folder 29)
    - Undated correspondence to Harriet Cooper from Sarah Cooper (Box 6, Folder 30)
    - Undated correspondence from Harriet Cooper to Sarah Cooper (Box 6, Folder 31)
    - Undated correspondence to and from Sarah's sister Irena Rawlings (Box 6, Folder 32)
    - Undated correspondence to and from Sarah's sister Harriet Skilton (Box 6, Folder 33)
    - Undated letters to Sarah Cooper, Authors' last names A-B (Box 7, Folder 16)
    - Undated letters to Sarah Cooper, Authors' last names: C-D (Box 7, Folder 17)
    - Undated letters to Sarah Cooper, Authors' last names: E-H (Box 7, Folder 18)
    - Undated letters to Sarah Cooper, Authors' last names: J-M (Box 7, Folder 19)
    - Undated letters to Sarah Cooper, Authors' last names: P (Box 7, Folder 20)
    - Undated letters to Sarah Cooper, Authors' last names: R-W (Box 7, Folder 21)
    - Calling Cards (Box 7, Folder 23)
    - Undated note from Sarah Cooper asking to be excused from visitors for the evening (Box 7, Folder 24)
    - Picture of Sarah Cooper's memorial statue with comments by Frank Skilton (Box 7, Folder 25)
    - Harriet Cooper's Hair (Box 7, Folder 26)
    - Braided hair of Ellen, Emma, and Miss C. Mills (Box 7, Folder 27)
    - Undated letter fragments and miscellany (Box 7, Folder 28)
  - Robert Ingersoll Material
    - Robert Ingersoll correspondence 1877 (Box 6, Folder 34)
    - Robert Ingersoll correspondence 1878 (Box 6, Folder 35)
    - Robert Ingersoll correspondence 1879 (Box 6, Folder 36)
    - Robert Ingersoll correspondence 1880-1885 (Box 6, Folder 37)
    - Robert Ingersoll correspondence 1886-1892 (Box 6, Folder 38)
    - Robert Ingersoll correspondence 1896-1916 (Box 6, Folder 39)
    - Robert Ingersoll essays and lectures:Liberty of Man, Woman, and Child, 1877, 1880 (Box 6, Folder 40)
    - Robert Ingersoll essays and lectures:The Coming and Going Religion, misc 1878-1879 (Box 6, Folder 41)
    - Robert Ingersoll essays and lectures:Mistakes of Ingersoll as shown by Professor Swing..., 1880 (Box 6, Folder 42)
    - Robert Ingersoll essays and lectures:Ingersoll's Answer to Professor Swing, 1880 (Box 6, Folder 43)
    - Robert Ingersoll essays and lectures:Ingersoll Under the Microscope, by J. M. Buckley, D.D. 1892 (Box 6, Folder 44)
    - Robert Ingersoll essays and lectures:Walt Whitman funeral address; Life, 1892, 1893 (Box 6, Folder 45)
    - Robert Ingersoll essays and lectures:Richard Ingersoll and Some of his Descendants, 1909 (Box 6, Folder 46)
    - Robert Ingersoll essays and lectures:Which Way?, 1910 (Box 6, Folder 47)
    - Robert Ingersoll essays and lectures:Robert G. Ingersoll, by Charles T. Gorham 1921 (Box 6, Folder 48)
  - Heresy Trial
    - Correspondence pertaining to Sarah Cooper's heresy trial, Statement from Bible Class 1882 (Box 7, Folder 1)
    - The Reasons Why- Statement by Sarah Cooper on why she chose to leave the Presbyterian Church 1892 (Box 7, Folder 2)
    - The Reasons Why- Scrap copies (Box 7, Folder 3)
  - Frances Willard, Susan B. Anthony, and Anna Howard Shaw Correspondence
    - Frances Willard letters 1883-1890 (Box 7, Folder 4)
    - Frances Willard letters 1891-1894 (Box 7, Folder 5)
    - Susan B. Anthony letters 1888-1895 (Box 7, Folder 6)
    - Susan B. Anthony letters - Lucy and Mary Anthony 1896-1905 (Box 7, Folder 7)
    - Anna Howard Shaw letters Jan. 1895-Oct. 1895 (Box 7, Folder 12)
    - Anna Howard Shaw letters Nov. 1895-Dec. 1895 (Box 7, Folder 13)
    - Anna Howard Shaw letters Jan. 1896-Apr. 1896 (Box 7, Folder 14)
    - Anna Howard Shaw letters May 1896-Dec. 1896 (Box 7, Folder 15)
  - Reverend Brown Affair
    - Brown Affair 1892-1895 (Box 7, Folder 8)
    - Sarah Cooper's Statement on the Brown affair 1896 (Box 7, Folder 29)
    - Brown Affair Jan. 1896-Feb. 1896 (Box 7, Folder 9)
    - Brown Affair Mar. 1896-Dec. 1897 (Box 7, Folder 10)
    - Brown Affair 1896-1897 (Box 7, Folder 11)
  - Diaries
    - Sarah Cooper Diaries: 1862 (Box 11, Folder 1)
    - Sarah Cooper Diaries: 1863 (Box 11, Folder 2)
    - Sarah Cooper Diaries: 1864 (Box 11, Folder 3)
    - Sarah Cooper Diaries: 1865 (Box 11, Folder 4)
    - Sarah Cooper Diaries: 1866 (Box 11, Folder 5)
    - Sarah Cooper Diaries: 1867 (Box 11, Folder 6)
    - Sarah Cooper Diaries: 1868 (Box 11, Folder 7)
    - Sarah Cooper Diaries: 1869 (Box 11, Folder 8)
    - Sarah Cooper Diaries: 1870 (Box 11, Folder 9)
    - Sarah Cooper Diaries: 1871 (Box 11, Folder 10)
    - Sarah Cooper Diaries: 1872 (Box 11, Folder 11)
    - Sarah Cooper Diaries: 1873 (Box 11, Folder 12)
    - Sarah Cooper Diaries: 1874, 1875 (Box 11, Folder 13)
    - Sarah Cooper Diaries: 1876, 1877 (Box 11, Folder 14)
    - Sarah Cooper Diaries: 1878, 1879 (Box 11, Folder 15)
    - Sarah Cooper Diaries: 1880, 1881 (Box 11, Folder 16)
    - Sarah Cooper Diaries: 1882, 1883 (Box 11, Folder 17)
    - Sarah Cooper Diaries: 1884, 1885 (Box 11, Folder 18)
    - Sarah Cooper Diaries: 1886, 1887 (Box 11, Folder 19)
    - Sarah Cooper Diaries: 1888, 1889 (Box 11, Folder 20)
    - Sarah Cooper Diaries: 1890, 1891 (Box 11, Folder 21)
    - Sarah Cooper Diaries: 1892, 1893 (Box 12, Folder 1)
    - Sarah Cooper Diaries: 1894, 1895 (Box 12, Folder 2)
    - Sarah Cooper Diaries: 1896 (Box 12, Folder 3)
    - Pages from Harriet Cooper's Diary: 1868 (Box 12, Folder 4)
    - Harriet Cooper Diaries: 1873, 1874 (Box 12, Folder 5)
    - Harriet Cooper Diaries: 1875, 1876 (Box 12, Folder 6)
    - Harriet Cooper Diaries: 1877, 1878 (Box 12, Folder 7)
    - Harriet Cooper Diaries: 1879, 1880 (Box 12, Folder 8)
    - Harriet Cooper Diaries: 1881, 1882 (Box 12, Folder 9)
    - Harriet Cooper Diaries: 1883 (Box 12, Folder 10)
- Series II. Writings
  - The Bankrupt's Daughter
    - Chapter 1 (Box 7, Folder 31)
    - Chapter 2 (Box 7, Folder 32)
    - Chapter 3 (Box 7, Folder 33)
    - Chapter 4 (Box 7, Folder 34)
    - Chapter 5 (Box 7, Folder 35)
    - Chapter 6 (Box 7, Folder 36)
    - Chapter 7 (Box 7, Folder 37)
    - Chapter 8 (Box 7, Folder 38)
    - Chapter 9 (Box 7, Folder 39)
    - Chapter 10 (Box 7, Folder 40)
    - Chapter 11 (Box 7, Folder 41)
    - Chapter 12 (Box 7, Folder 42)
    - Chapter 13 (Box 7, Folder 43)
    - Chapter 14 (Box 7, Folder 44)
    - Chapter 15 (Box 7, Folder 45)
    - Chapter 16 (Box 7, Folder 46)
    - Chapter 17 (Box 7, Folder 47)
    - Chapter 18 (Box 7, Folder 48)
    - Chapter 19 (Box 7, Folder 49)
    - Chapter 20 (Box 7, Folder 50)
    - Chapter 21 (Box 7, Folder 51)
    - Chapter 22 (Box 7, Folder 52)
    - Chapter 23 (Box 7, Folder 53)
    - Chapter 24 (Box 7, Folder 54)
    - Chapter 25 (Box 7, Folder 55)
    - Chapter 26 (Box 7, Folder 56)
    - Chapter 27 (Box 7, Folder 57)
    - Chapter 28 (Box 7, Folder 58)
    - Chapter 29 (Box 7, Folder 59)
    - Chapter 30 (Box 7, Folder 60)
    - Chapter 31 (Box 7, Folder 61)
    - Chapter 32 (Box 7, Folder 62)
    - Chapter 33 (Box 7, Folder 63)
    - Chapter 34 (Box 7, Folder 64)
    - Chapter 35 (Box 7, Folder 65)
    - Chapter 36 (Box 7, Folder 66)
    - Chapter 37 (Box 7, Folder 67)
    - Chapter 38 (Box 7, Folder 68)
    - Chapter 39 (Box 7, Folder 69)
    - Chapter 40 (Box 7, Folder 70)